https://wbtai.com/privacy-statement/

Programs
Do You Remember These?
Careers
Listen Live!
Programs
Do You Remember These?
Careers
Listen Live!
WBTA Main Stream
LeRoy Sports Stream
Privacy Statement
Privacy Statement
WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York does not read any of your private online communications.
WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York and WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York collects and uses your personal information to operate the WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York Web site and deliver the services you have requested. WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York and its affiliates. WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
video porno italiani
WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York, in order to determine what WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York pages, or register with WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York site or services, a cookie helps WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York is protecting your information.
Contact Information
WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York has not adhered to this Statement, please contact WBTA AM 1490 Batavia, New York at webmaster@mcpinc.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
WBTA
Search
Contacts
https://wbtai.com
(585) 344-1490
feedback@wbtai.com
113 Main Street, Batavia, NY 14020
About us
WBTA is the only radio station directly serving Genesee County offering News, Weather, Local Sports, Radio Auctions, Obituaries, and Local Personalities.
Discover more
Site Info
Site Design and Hosting by Marchese Computer Products, Inc. Serving Genesee County and the surrounding area since 1981.
Listen Live!
[There are no radio stations in the database]
